MARY LE

A product manager with a solid background in UX Research, UI Design, and Front-end development.

EDUCATION

Cornell University | Ithaca, NY

MAY 2018

Masters in Information Science

UC Irvine | Irvine, CA

JUNE 2011

Bachelor of Arts in International Studies & Sociology

EXPERIENCE

Cornell Johnson Graduate School of Management | Ithaca, NY

Web Developer Assistant | 09.2017 - Present

• Manage website contents and conduct user research with students.

Northwestern Polytechnic University | Fremont, CA

Front-end developer | 04.2016 - 07.2017

- Created designs for recruiting and marketing events and web contents.
- Implemented new web pages and improved upon existing pages to make them more dynamic.

Mobile Action | San Francisco, CA

Front-end web developer | 05.2015 - 12.2015

- Spearheaded UI design and development for all products and web pages.
- Designed new email templates and conducted A/B testings.

Achievers | San Francisco, CA

Front-end web developer | 04.2015 - 07.2017

- Developed the relaunch for the corporate website.
- Built a mobile survey application that is used at marketing events to gather prospective client data.

Freelance | Bay Area, CA

UI developer | 08.2014 - 04.2015

• Established client relationships and completed all design and development project deliverables.

ABOUT ME

maryle.me

linkedin.com/in/maaaryle

Ithaca, NY (650) 918-7855 mnl46@cornell.edu

SKILLS & TOOLS

UX Research

1:1 interviews, affinity diagrams, personas, heuristic evaluation, usability testing, journey mapping, user-centered design methods, lo-fidelity prototyping

UI Design

mockups, wireframes, Adobe Photoshop/ Illustrator/InDesign, InVision, Sketch, Balsamiq, UXPin

Development

HTML, CSS (Sass, LESS, Bootstrap), Javascript (jQuery), C++, Java, MongoDB, Express.js, Angular.js, Node.js, Git, Heroku, WordPress, Drupal